keywordmax.com 2003-12-03

# KEYWORD RANKING | Keyword Bid Management | Keyword Optimization | KeywordMax

##### Privacy Statement for Direct Response Technologies, Inc.

Direct Response has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the following web sites: http://directleads.com , http://directtrack.com , http://directresponse.com , http://keywordmax.com , http://giftcards.com , http://mycoupons.com 

**To contact us, regarding any privacy concerns, you can reach us at:**

Direct Response Technologies, Inc.  
PO Box 16530  
Pittsburgh, PA 15242  
USA  
info@directresponse.com  
412-921-6881  

Disputes arising in connection with the privacy statement will be resolved by our web site's customer service representative Errors or wrongful actions arising in connection with our privacy policy will be remedied by our service. http://directresponse.com/contact.html. Contact by email at office@directresponse.com, by phone, or by homepage. Errors or wrongful actions arising in connection with our privacy policy will be remedied by our service. 

**We provide the following level of access to users information collected on this site:**   
MyCoupons.com users, DirectResponse.com Advertisers, and GiftCards.com users can see their profiles and their account information.

**We collect the following types of information:**   
All of our sites: Dynamic Information: Http Cookies 

Where we sell product or service, we gather personal information and credit information. 

**We use this information for:**   
For Cookies: Web Site and System Administration

For Personal Information or Credit Card information: we use it to charge clients and enable us to reach customers and clients with the products or services purchased.

**This data may be shared with:**   
For Personal Information or Credit Card information: Ourselves and/or our agents

For cookies: We retain this information Data retained only for amount of time necessary to complete a single online interaction. 

**How Data is Collected:**   
_DirectLeads:_ Signing up for the DirectLeads Advertising Network provides Direct Response Technologies, Inc with your name, email address, company name, SS#/TIN, web address, traffic, and zip code. Our method of collection is through our register page. After a potential affiliate enters his/her information on the signup page, that data is transferred to our server and is set on the back side to 'evaluate' whether they will conform to our network requirements.

_MyCoupons:_ Signing up for the MyCoupons™ provides Direct Response Technologies, Inc with your name, email address, gender, and zip code. Our method of collection is through our register page (http://www.mycoupons.com/signup/signup.php). After a subscriber enters his/her name, email address, year of birth, gender, and zip code, data is transferred to our server and an email account is setup. 

_DirectCertificates:_ Through out the site, customers have the option of submitting their information to DirectCertificates. Our primary method of collection is through our registration page. Signing up for the DirectCertificates program provides Direct Response Technologies, Inc with your name, email address, company name, address information, and credit card informational of which is collected over a secure server. Additionally, users have the option of submitting information via e-mail within the customer service, and/or the contact us section(s). On our Merchant Partner section, merchants can enter address information, what kind of business they have, and if they would like to be listed as a merchant within the site. Affiliate information (business name, address and URL) is used to sign up a company that wishes to become a member of the DirectCertificates affiliate program. 

_DirectCoupons Newsletter:_ Signing up for the DirectCoupons™ Weekly Newsletter provides Direct Response Technologies, Inc with only your name, email address, and possibly zip code. Our method of collection is through our Subscriber page (http://www.directcoupons.com). After a subscriber enters his/her name, email address, and zip code, data is transferred to a 'hold' position. The subscriber then receives an email requesting CONFIRMATION. After the confirmation email is returned to our mail-server, the subscriber is entered into the DirectCoupons™ database and mailing list. Subscribers may also send a blank email message to our subscribe email address, and the same process is undertaken. We only use subscriber information in order to send our newsletter. 

**How the Information is used:**   
_DirectLeads:_ We gather your information in order to evaluate whether you are a good fit to become an affiliate in the DirectLeads Advertising Network. If you are accepted as an affiliate, then a Welcome Email is sent to you, and your information is transferred to our database server. If you are not selected as an approved affiliate, then your record is deleted and we do not keep the information.

_MyCoupons:_ MyCoupons™ free email account allows you to forward email received from your MyCoupons™ address to any existing email account of your choosing. It also allows you to simply read and send email from the web browser. We do not read users email. We only email your MyCoupons™ email box, unless we find a problem with your account, then we will email your regular email address. The other demographical data is used only to profile our general user base, and not to market to accordingly. 

_DirectCertificates:_ DirectCertificates uses this information only to activate and verify accounts, as well to assist members in the ordering process and to process reminder e-mails they have requested; this is done for the overall convenience of the membership. The information may be aggregated on a monthly basis to determine the demographic make up of the user base. Any and all information used in this process is for the sole and exclusive use of Direct Response Technologies, Inc. 

_DirectCoupons Newsletter:_ DirectCoupons™ Weekly Newsletter is sent to subscribers every week. It contains various coupons and freebies found throughout the Internet. Direct Response Technologies, Inc. does not take responsibility for the specific offers found in the DirectCoupons™ Weekly Newsletter. 

**With Whom will information be shared:**   
Direct Response Technologies, Inc., holds all data gathered in strict confidence. Under no circumstances will your e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, SS#, be sold to, supplied to, or otherwise made available to any third party. 

**The Site Opt-Out Policy**   
Affiliate Partners, Subscribers, or Customers can opt-out at any time. You can email office@directstuff.com and ask to have the account removed immediately - we will remove you for our system within 24 hours after request.

**Links to other sites:**   
We link to many other sites from our Properties. Please check with the sites that we link to for their Privacy Policies. 

**Cookie Policy:**   
We actively use cookies to place on users computers to track leads and clicks to advertisers programs. The only purposes of placing cookies is to enable us to track a user through the links to track clicks or leads in real time, as well as to remember you when you return to our sites to make log in easier.
